Greater Hartford Jewish Community Center Collection 0008.120.001
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Photo Series IV: Senior Adults
  - Senior Adults/volunteers assisting with mailings, undated
- Photo Series V: General Administration
  - General Administration/Anniversaries/80th, undated
  - General Administration/Annual Meetings, undated
  - General Administration/Board of Directors/Members, undated
  - General Administration/Board Members/Active lay members, undated
  - General Administration/Buildings/91 Vine Street, Hartford, undated
  - General Administration/Buildings/1015 Asylum Ave., Hartford, 1949
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford, 1962
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/General, undated
  - General Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/Field House/Groundbreaking, 2006, undated
  - Administration/Buildings/335 Bloomfield Ave., West Hartford/expansion, 1990
  - General Administration/Buildings/Sculpture and Art/Holocaust Memorial, undated
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1983
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1984
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1985
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1986
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1987
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1988
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1989
- Photo Series VI: General Administration
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1990
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1991
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1992
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1993
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1994
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1995
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1996
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, 1997
  - General Administration/Buildings/Fundraising/Annual Scholarship Fund Gala, undated
  - General Administration/Staff, undated
  - General Administration/Staff and lay, undated
  - General Administration/members and membership, undated
- Photo Series VII: Early Childhood Center
  - Early Childhood Center, undated
  - Early Childhood Center, 1950s, 1950-1959
  - Early Childhood Center, 1960s, 1960-1969
  - Early Childhood Center, 1970s-1980s, 1970-1989
  - Early Childhood Center, 1970-1974
  - Early Childhood Center, 1975-1979
  - Early Childhood Center, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Early Childhood Center, 1990s, 1990-1999
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, undated
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1950s, 1950-1959
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah,, 1960s, 1960-1969
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Early Childhood Center/Campareenah, 1990s, 1990-1999
- Photo Series VIII: Youth Services
  - Youth Services/Athletic programs, undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Dance, undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Entertainment programs, undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Holidays, undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Jonathan's Dream playground (Barzach family), undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Miscellaneous, 2 folders, undated
  - Youth Services/Children/Theater, undated
  - Youth Services/"Junior Debs", undated
  - Youth Services/Teens/College preparation program, undated
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1950s and earlier, 1950-1959
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1960s, 1960-1969
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1970s, 1970-1979
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1980s, 1980-1989
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, 1990s, 1990-1999
  - Youth Services/Teens/Miscellaneous, undated
  - Youth Services/Teens/new teen lounge, 1980
  - Youth Services/Teens/Theater program, 2 folders, undated
  - Youth Services/Teens/Travel, undated